

Ravi Patel

Senior UI/UX Designer

- Born on November 16,1992
- Lives in Ahmedabad, India

Hi! I'm Ravi - a UI/UX designer based in Ahmedabad. My work is deeply rooted in clean and typographic approach, with think outside the box mindset.

Combining research, strategy and visual best practices to create distinct impactful experiences.

I completed my Bachelor Degree in Computer engineering at the Universal Collage of Engineering & Technology in Ahmedabad.

- +91 7016063230, +91 9427972225
- patelravi1611@gmail.com
- A https://patelravi1611.github.io/
- in www.linkedin.com/in/patelravi1611/

Bē www.behance.net/patelravi1611

Work Experience

Jetbro Pvt. Ltd.

Senior UI/UX Designer And Developer (2017 - Present)

Step2Websoft Technology

UI/UX Designer And Developer (2016 - 2017)

Shreedhoon Technology

Web Designer (2014 - 2015)

Freelance

UI/UX Designer And Developer (2014 - Present)

Education

Universal Collage of Engineering & Technology

Class of 2010; Computer engineer

Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe illustrator
- Adobe Xd
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Interaction Design

- Mobile UI Design
- Responsive Design & Development
- HTML,CSS,JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS

Language

- English (Professional Working Proficiency)
- Hindi (Native or Bilingual Proficiency)
- Gujarati (Native or Bilingual Proficiency)